petrasplanet.com 2016-04-03

# Discover Petra’s Planet and enjoy the benefits of Membership! | Petra’s Planet

**November 1st  2015**

This privacy statement describes how Dramaforum Oy (“Dramaforum”) collects and uses the personal information you provide on our Web site: www.petrasplanet.com and in our app: Incredipets. It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information. 

If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us through our contact page

## 1\. PRIVO® Privacy Assurance Program 

Dramaforum is a licensee of the PRIVO® Privacy Assurance  Program (“the Program”).As a participating member in the Program, Dramaforum adheres to the strict information collection, use and disclosure requirements. PRIVO is an independent, third-party organization committed to safeguarding children's personal information collected online. PRIVO aims to help parents and their children exercise control over personal information while exploring the Internet. The certification seal posted on this page indicates that Dramaforum has established COPPA compliant privacy practices and has agreed to submit to PRIVO's oversight and consumer dispute resolution process. If you have questions or concerns about our privacy practices, please contact us at +358 40 534 8157 or our contact page. If you have further concerns after you have contacted us, you can contact PRIVO directly at privacy@privo.com 

## 2\. Name of Controller

Dramaforum Oy   
Vaisalantie 4, Innopoli 3  
FI-02130 Espoo   
Finland

## 3\. Name of the Data File 

Petra's Planet and Incredipets (the "Service") End User Database

## 4\. Collected Information 

Petra's Planet's and Incredipets collect the following information: 

  * User Data
  * Player's Login Name and Password (the Login Name cannot be seen publicly) 
  * Player's Avatar Name
  * Parent's Email Address 
  * Billing Information such as credit card

## 5\. Purpose of Collection 

The personal information is collected for purposes of maintaining the client relationship and for developing the Service. The personal information may also be used for communication purposes with clients and for sending you newsletters and marketing communications. If you wish to subscribe to our newsletter(s), we will use email address to send the newsletter to you. An option to subscribe is available on the Parents section from Petra's Planet Web site.  Out of respect for your privacy, you may choose to stop receiving our newsletter or marketing emails by following the unsubscribe instructions included in these emails, accessing the email preferences in your account settings page or you can contact us through our [contact page](http://petrasplanet.com/contact-us)

Payment information is not stored.

## 6\. Source of the Information 

The personal information is obtained directly from the user of the Service and his or her legal guardian in the following situations:

  1. when the user registers at the Service;
  2. when the user accesses and uses the Service; and
  3. when the user makes purchases in or via the Service.

Certain information is also collected automatically by means of cookies. Please see Section 9 for more information.

## 7\. Erroneous, Incomplete or Obsolete Information; Right of Inspection 

Dramaforum does not verify the correctness of the personal information. A user who has logged into the Service may view, correct or delete his user information and purchase history stored in the data file by emailing our Customer Support through  [our contact page](http://petrasplanet.com/contact-us)

If you would like to request an update or deletion of your child's information or refuse further collection, use or contact by the site please contact us through http://petrasplanet.com/contact-us 

A child's participation in or ability to access an activity will not be conditioned on them providing more personal information than is reasonably necessary for that activity.

Parents have the right to consent to our collection and use of personal information from their kids without also consenting to our disclosure of such information to third parties.

In addition, in accordance with Section 26 of the Personal Data Act, the user has the right to inspect all information regarding him stored in the Petra's Planet and Incredipets End User Database. The right of inspection may be used by contacting Dramaforum. If the user of the Service is a minor, his or her legal guardian may use the right of inspection on his or her behalf. However, Dramaforum reserves the right not to disclose personal information from the database to a person claiming to be the legal guardian of a user if the person demanding the disclosure of personal information does not provide such evidence as may be required by Dramaforum to establish his or her identity and/or relationship to the respective user. In addition, Dramaforum reserves the right not to disclose personal information to legal guardian of a user if the user is at least 15 years old and objects the disclosure.

## 8\. Disclosures 

Generally Dramaforum does not disclose personal information to any third parties. However, Dramaforum may disclose personal information to such a third party who Dramaforum uses to provide the Service where such disclosure is necessary for the provision of the Service. These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us.

  * Our shopping cart is hosted by our e-commerce solutions provider. They host our ordering system, and collect your billing information directly from you for the purpose of processing your order. This company does not use this information for any other purpose. See the Third Parties Section for more details.
  * In addition, Dramaforum may disclose information to the police in connection with criminal investigation and to officials where required by law such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request. The information shall not be disclosed to countries outside the EEA.
  * If Dramaforum is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information.
  * To any other third party with your prior consent to do so.

## 9\. Deletion of Information 

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services contact us through our contact page. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. Notwithstanding the foregoing, payment data is retained for such period of time as is required for accounting purposes or as may be required for the fulfillment of other statutorily obligations.

## 10\. Cookies 

In order to monitor and enable the use of the Service, cookies may be stored from time to time to the user's computer. The cookies are used to collect information specified in this Privacy Policy for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy. In addition, cookies are used by Dramaforum and/or its partners to monitor the number of visitors at the Service. When used for these purposes, the cookies are not used to collect personal information or other such information that could be connected or a single user.

If you do not wish to permit the storage of cookies on your computer, you may disable cookies from the settings of your Internet browser. Due to the nature of the Service it is impossible to use the Service without enabling cookies and thus if you do not wish to enable cookies, you cannot use the Service.

The use of cookies by our partners, affiliates, tracking utility company, and service providers is not covered by our privacy policy.  We do not have access or control over these cookies.  Our partners, affiliates, tracking utility company, service providers use session ID cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site, in order for you to use the shopping cart, etc.

Our Web pages contain electronic images known as Web beacons (sometimes called single-pixel gifs) and are used along with cookies to compile aggregated statistics to analyze how our site is used and may be used in some of our emails to let us know which emails and links have been opened by recipients. This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of our customer communications and marketing campaigns.

## 11\. Data Security 

Access to user's personal information is limited to such persons who need to have such access for the purposes of their work obligations. Such persons consist of user care and technical maintenance personnel of Dramaforum.

The security of your personal information is important to us.  We follow generally accepted standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it.  No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however.  Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

## 12\. Links to 3rd Party Sites

Our Site includes links to other Web sites whose privacy practices may differ from those of Dramaforum Oy. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy policies. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy policy of any Web site you visit.

## 13\. Third Parties

We work with Google Analytics to better understand your use of our site and improve your experience. This third party is prohibited from sharing your data. For more information, please visit: [www.google.com/analytics](http://www.google.com/analytics)

Petra's Planet works with third party PaymentWall to process your payments. We do not store payment information. PaymentWall is prohibited from sharing your data. For more information, please visit: [www.paymentwall.com](http://www.paymentwall.com/)

## 14\. Social Media Widgets

Our Web site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button and Widgets, such as the Share this button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site. These features are only available in the parent section of the website. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

## 15\. Blog/Forum

Our Web site offers publicly accessible blogs or community forums that allows you to post a comment. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. To request removal of your personal information from our blog or community forum, contact us through http://petrasplanet.com/contact-us. In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.

## 16\. Changes to this Policy

Dramaforum may make changes to this Privacy Policy from time to time for any reason. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used. If we make changes in the way we use Personal Information or Children's Personal Information, we will notify you via email or by posting an announcement on the Website prior to the change becoming effective. Users are bound by any changes to the Privacy Policy when he or she uses the Website after such changes have been first posted.

**Company information**   
If you want to know more about Dramaforum check our homepage:   
[www.dramaforum.fi/en](http://www.dramaforum.fi/en)  or if you have questions about this privacy policy, you can send us a mail at the address below.

Dramaforum Oy   
Vaisalantie 4, Innopoli 3  
FI-02130 Espoo  
Finland  
+358 40 534 8157
